I ate, no, now
It's half past 1 now.
fifth
It will come when there are some guests.
5 My God No Hello
Ah
5 my god
hi
Welcome then
Welcome to the leader
thank you
nice to meet you thank you so much
hello yes nice
to meet you grandma
yes yes yes
Nice to meet you
i'm Daniel nice to meet you i'm Daniel this is
beautiful nice to meet you
you guys wanna have a seat yeah
yeah perfect
thank you
this is so nice
Haha so much
They are a trendy couple, so pretty
regenerative cream
i need to stop using makeup
wipes
so we're gonna throw those away
and then yeah
try this it's so good
the latte banana
kind of tea
it sounded good i almost got it when i saw that
oh my gosh that's so yummy
i'm excited for dinner
hello
how are you good how are you
i'm brenna
nice to meet you
hi nice to meet you
thank you
follow me
to the consultation room
this is our consultation room
thank you so much thank you
good good excited
you're excited yes i am excited
oh
you're you're
working in fashion business
i do yeah yes
you know what is good for you
and what fits you
right yes i think
clothing wise i know what i like
but i
could definitely use some help
with the
skincare and all of that
skincare and makeup and hair
things about
makeup and hair
yeah do you have any
specific style
you want
i really want to surprise
my fiance we got engaged
um back in December
we've been together
for six years now in may
and then we got engaged
this past December
so i'm getting married next may
he's always so nice
about everything
and he's always
saying that i look good so
no matter what i knew that it was gonna
be sweet but
i expected him to have
a little bit more surprise
than usual
and then
usually a light bit of makeup
like a little bit of concealer
a little bit of mascara
um
today i don't have anything on
just fresh
so i wanted to do something
a little bit more sultry
and like sexy
do something a little bit more
sultry
yeah different side of you
my name is brenna i am
twenty five years old
and i work
as a fashion office manager
i don't do a lot with beauty
generally
i just wanted
to be able to surprise
him with something
a little bit different
a little bit more sultry and
exciting
thank you
have a seat thank you so much
here's a blanket
oh my goodness thank you
so nice
it's gonna be best service
oh okay i'm excited
okay
i'm gonna recline your chair
yeah perfect just relax okay
my gosh so fancy
did you born in New York
no i'm from florida
originally oh florida
yeah all right and did you meet
fiance at school
no i met him back home
we moved up together so
my fiance works there
he's a Somali
so he does the wine stuff there
oh really at a restaurant yeah
how was it
it was so nice and relaxing
i'm like i need to do this more often
score ten out of ten
yeah ten out of ten
thousand out of ten wow
wow really
my god
Shampoo and eat again, okay?
Oh, I told you to just look here.
Oh, I'm trying to stop you from doing this again.
You can't eat anymore.
I couldn't eat, so I left that open.
Should we stop together?
ya okay yeah
Oh, eat it. Come on, eat it all.
Okay, I'm hungry. Ah, I'm hungry.
um
5 Sounds delicious 5
It was delicious, but yeah
안 드셨죠 응
왜요 왠지 먹을 거야
oh my gosh
look at all this makeup
hi my name is Leo
nice to meet you
brenna yes yes yes
thank you so much
thank you so much for coming i'm trying not to move my head
so that
things don't fall off
no i'm excited
i've never had my hair makeup
professionally done before
so this is huge for me yeah
i'm really
appreciate to come
coming here oh my god
yes no thank you
so appreciate it
i'm very excited me too
i think my fiance
is gonna be excited too
oh really yeah
so have you go abroad recently
have i gone abroad recently
um
i went to Italy with my mom
Italy oh
i love italy
we're getting
married in Paris though
Paris through Paris
in Paris Paris
yeah yeah that'll be next year
though wow
5 My God Yes
Are you here my customer?
thank you yet
After doing this, you will go to the temple now.
That person is still a bit old
Thank you, how much time is left, sister?
me
Sentiya has arrived
Okay
In the meantime, I have to clean up here.
It's so dirty right away
You'll come in.
Wow why why why no
Am I organizing it?
Is it because it's my older sister's style?
No, it's okay, you can organize it.
Uh okay okay and three three
Take out the puff
If you let me go, okay okay okay
Okay, one wet tissue.
Lay it down
shithead shithead yeah
Go quickly, come quickly, go quickly
Is it right to do it this way?
are you okay
I need to eat
Even if it's just chicken, no, no, no, no.
I can't eat now
No, I can eat it all the time.
It's all chaining now.
Oh, it's not chaining, it's completely
It's going well now, yeah
Oh, let's come to our senses, really.
okay
oh thank you
thank you for your patience
oh my gosh of course
today i'm just enjoying relaxing
yeah i know this is so lovely
thank you
hmm
uh
what's your dress color
oh mine is like a brownish green
oh really
brown green
it's like a brownish
ah like a olive green yeah
kind of yeah it's like an olive
each color
hmm
i wonder
what's the match the dress
my favorite color
Hey, maybe
To Piyangse over there
Can you see the color of that dress?
If you ask me, yes
Hey Waristek Ah
This is it
That's right, olive green
Ah so pretty
I think it'll be pretty
It's khaki. Khaki then.
Wait a minute then
uh
Mr. Leo, by any chance
Can you lend me your shadow?
What what
Oh, are you out of your mind? Do something.
I can't hear well
Maybe khaki or olive green?
There's the same shadow
I have it
Would you like to see some strawberries here?
Huh, I really like it
Thank you, I will use this and give it to you
do you want to buy like a sexy
i think yeah
i want it to be a little sexy
sultry maybe like something
sultry with the eyes yeah
search for a look
how can i do that
Because my eyes are so bright
Horizontal is sexy
It's easy to maintain style.
Because so many of them are together,
Ah, what should I do with this?
The further back the leash goes, the longer it gets.
Should I put it on or not?
Should I do it from the corner of my eye or
Should I extend the shadow?
many such things
Make-up artists get worried.
the
certri glam bold makeup for you
okay okay i'm excited
oh my god this is the camera
oh my god
So pretty
Ah
why wait
Oh really pink
Grandma, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, you look lonely
Health age C-Sabi C-Sabi yes uh
sssss
We're doing makeup together right now.
Yeah
Minyoung has a lot of talent, yes.
Omera, this one
I didn't stop, I didn't stop. I didn't stop.
Acne It's acne here.
Should I cover it? Yes.
you did art too
yes so if you did art yeah yeah
your natural
skin tone is really bright
that i have to mix
with the green
i'm being so pampered
i've got two people
doing my makeup
i feel like a star
you're a star here
Oh, good job, sister, really help me.
have
Look at my clean neck, there is nothing at all.
Please finish it a little bit. Yes.
So pretty
Golden hands, golden hands, come
i work
as a fashion office manager
i think clothing
wise i know what i like
i'm not great
at makeup
so it's usually just something
kind of
easy more
bare faced
we've been together
for six years
now and getting married next may
and i just wanted
to be able to surprise
him with something
a little bit different
a little bit more sultry
and exciting
thanks for
waiting your fiance is coming
in three minutes
Oh so cute
So are you coming? Are you coming?
If you hear footsteps, something is coming.
Hahaha
Because so many of them are together,
Hey, what should I do with this?
they tried to really color
match the eyeshadow
so they were gonna do a smoky
bold eye
and they tried to pick up
kind of similar
olive tone
Make your eyes a little bolder
Below the eyes
soft pitch
I think I was trying to use color.
things
that had more of a dramatic eye
um really glowy skin
with some kind of blush cheeks
and i think that they executed
that very well
머리로 이렇게 살짝
가려진 느낌 좋아
야 어 하하하 어 진짜 이쁘다
oh my goodness oh my goodness
i've never seen myself
look like this before
so i don't know what kind of magic
they work today
but they got it to do
what i've always wanted it to
마이
갓
have you ever seen my hair
this voluminous
no voluminous
no
wow
that's crazy right
i haven't even seen the
full whoa
it's crazy
thank you for waiting
thank you for waiting thank you
부끄러워
we're gonna have a great dinner
though
do you like the eyes
i could never do this myself
i don't think i could ever
have the
steady hands to do that
it's hard
you're beautiful thank you
thank you yeah
you don't need to go to Paris
yes
you guys should go for wedding
now
i need those cooling
pads again my face is so hot
Ah
Yes no, how many times do you do it?
My skin will become so sweet that it will disappear.
Because I wrote it, 5 My God Oh Me
I will really become that kind of husband
Oh, it's so sweet, but oh, it's cool.
Oh so so cool
Well done really
I need to drink water too, yeah
Oh now
It's time for Emma to come
If we finish without a fire
Welcome
Welcome to the class president
emma emma emma
miss friend yes what's your name Ellen Ellen yes so nice to meet you welcome to you as well say please hi have a seat here
so i got this
information about you
you are a chef
yes i am a famous chef
oh it's owner to you know
it's called aqua right aqua yes
i'm the executive chef
of a restaurant called aqua
in New York
my life is just cooking
it's kitchen
so
i've never been like the
the woman or the girl
who's like
take care of myself
it's it's all about work
i very rarely do makeup
i never have time for it
working 14 hours a day
it's just i don't care
i go into the kitchen and i work
and then hot in the kitchen
so it's it's very
very warm and dry
yes so you need then more
hydration than
i think so yes other people
right yeah
it's nice to be able to
learn a little
and see what i need to do
your routine for
cosmetic or
yeah they it's um
um a sunscreen lotion only
only yeah
okay less than two minutes okay
oh my gosh okay
i'm not very good at
yeah i can tell
i can finally understand
what they said
we're going to dinner tonight
i'm taking her to my restaurant
oh my gosh this especially
then
do you have a specific
style you want to make over
uh i was thinking a little bit
glam glam yeah
something different
i never really wear
makeup in the kitchen
uh huh so
i'm kind of curious and excited
to maybe see a little bit more
edge edge
okay
i always have my hair up
and i have very very thin
Scandinavian
hair so
it it's very very thin
it's super thin
very thin i have very
thin hair too
i trust you guys completely
you're the best at what you do
so
i feel like you trust
when you come to the restaurant
and you trust what i cook
yes i trust what you say
thank you for saying that
she's very bold
my name is Emma bankson
and i'm an executive chef
of a restaurant in New York
i've never had long hair
and makeup for me is very basic
i never really get to
have this glam feeling
i was curious to
experience something different
ready
follow me please
thank you
see you later
i can't wait to see you
today is your hair
stylist oh lovely i'm chaong
yes lovely meeting you
i checked your hair
yes please yes okay
i don't have very much hair
um um
Usually
Many time
Now this Sponite yeah ah
I really want to do volume eyes.
Yes, that's right.
My hair is too small
Okay, because the hair is like this, but
Wouldn’t that work too?
Peace Peace Yes, I meant to add it.
This is
It's a word that can't be put straight.
I tie my hair every day
Even if I raise it, I won’t receive it
I apologize because you said that
About a head
There is no food outside.
So I told him to take care of it.
It's so hard for me to do it myself
It's a situation.
What should I do with me?
I think it's very rude and trustworthy.
Brother, what should I do?
I thought about it
was it all right yes perfect
i just fell asleep yes
welcome
oh nice
yeah wow please
Could you please give me that too?
banana
Cushion Ah banana cushion okay
Okay
what's your name again Emma Emma
nice to meet you i'm leo
Leo lovely
i heard you want to glam look
yes excuse me
thank you
and i heard you're a chef
i am yes
always in the kitchen
oh yeah you're a chef
yes she is chef it's an honor
thank you well that's missed
skincare first okay
Skin care like this today
do you have any preferences
of the color
like pink orange brown brown
um i
completely trust you ah okay
okay cool
that's why i'm here right okay
like you do what you're
trust you
yes okay okay trust me
i'm so excited
um
My hair is all dried.
I'm so brainless
How about just knowing?
I'm just worried.
Do you need anything? No, not now.
what's your skincare routine
um
not very good
i do a moisturizer
moisturizers and one and
that's it oh the simple one
yeah okay
do you have any
do you have any skincare problem
uh no no
no concern
i mean i know it's dry
but uh dry skin
i'm not very good at it
excuse me
and today
i applied this
wigoo do you like it
yes yeah how do you
i check the hair color
예스 오케이
좀 다른 컬러라서 찾아야겠다
예 가져갈까요 어 누구 거야
so how long have you
uh chef been a chef
i've been a chef for
twenty five years
wow
time goes fast yeah
are you still love cooking
i still
love cooking all the time
everyday
wow um yeah oh wow
so what restaurant are you
are you in
it's a Nordic
Nordic restaurant in your
wow wow
yeah
i'm from Sweden
Sweden so yeah from Stockholm
Stockholm so why you come
to New York
for restaurant for
restaurant yes i wanted more
i wanted more energy
bigger yeah yeah
and what's bigger than New York
to start but
have you always wanted
to do makeup yeah
i love makeup yeah
i'm so lucky
to have
this kind of job you know right
yeah me too
okay and let's do
with eyeshadow with
this glam look what about like
Oh okay oh why oh why
Hey ah why ok don’t s
don s
Haha okay
Passion for your dream
He was a person who really poured his heart out.
Because I am a person who ran like a racetrack, I
Because I probably didn’t take much care of it.
I really took this opportunity
A time to find a new me
Let me have it
It looks like this to me too
Because I can be surprised
I really wanted to give you a surprise.
So
really full
Let’s go glam, I feel gorgeous
Like this
Something like manners, something like an idea.
I want to feel this way
maybe
it's gonna be look good on rose
or like this red
like this color
red rose
maybe it looks really good
yeah roses your color yeah
this looks really good
i don't really
feel like i need it right
I'm there to cook
right not look good
right
just focus on cooking right yeah
which means when i do get a
night off
or go outside it's
it's nice to
right look pretty
eyeliner let's go eyeliner
That last person
Yeah, I don't have much hair, so that's why
How do I survive
There’s nowhere to go, moon moon, moon moon
You don't have the strength
Oh, so I ate it.
Should I put it in the future?
I thought
uh where is it
I brought this without knowing.
But
It's okay to put it on
My hair is too much
No, just
I think I can see all the ticks, right?
So how much do you want to live?
But I can attach it
Dryer dryer book dryer only
I just need it.
Ice and Using the Isen
Hair wiggnen i use the isen is this is i aigl igle yes okay is okay
After thinking about it, I actually actually
Get a full wig
have to write
In this case, I have to do it.
I told you to roll your eyelashes
There is something you use to attach it, right?
It's harmless to the human body.
With that, I made some pieces, one by one.
Attach one stitch to look like your original hair
Okay is very easy to manage
Okay this time yes yes this time yes
Wait a minute. It's better to stick it on this side.
Yes check on this side too
yes check
together
S Lily B Call
Hold here and press
continue
Here and here too
Remove as much as possible
I'm trying to make it easy for you.
In the same color
yes the same color
Hey, isn't it over yet? Hey, Pony.
teacher
Oh right
You have a lot of sense
It's pretty, yeah
A bit of work
Yes, I have a job.
I heard a lot about that baby
I have a head for work
Oh yeah yeah
It's okay now, teacher.
Okay yes it's okay yes
Just put it on a little bit
It will be easy to take off.
Because I did it in four places.
oh wow it's like your
your lashes yes
I feel like a celebrity
having four people
working on me
Should I still put it on just once? Take a breath now.
Because of breathing
I'm going to change the color of this.
Wait a minute
For this, I have to mix two colors again. It's awkward right now, so I don't have Sam's color.
Write these three
There's no way it's the same now
Hey, how do you do this?
1st 1st Godan Island
I'll bring a knife and do it over there again.
If you just remove this from what you see,
Okay, wait a minute.
Wait a minute
This looks much more like his own head.
10,000 connections only
looks amazing
yeah
Yeah
That's enough
uh
Hahaha
Wow
It's Gray Salt.
Wow, now I put it on
I can cut and do your hair for you.
I think you can add volume as well.
Ah, right now, Emma is number one.
No. 1, I’m looking forward to it. Emma is perfect.
You become a completely different person, you become a completely different person.
today's score
To put it in perspective
I think the highest point will come out.
score changes
두 개 스크램블에서 먹었지
빵 먹었지
하이 하이
ㅎㅎ
i love you 아빠도
6 아 비포 앤 앱토 ㅎㅎ 5 예스
왓츠 6 닉 엘런 엘런 예스
well she's
gonna be dressed up for dinner
so i figured yeah
i need to match right yeah yeah
right
i've gotta look fabulous at aqua
it's a wonderful restaurant
and you know she took it from
one to two
Michelin stars oh
we love it
uh this was ten years ago
oh she was the pastry chef
and then she got promoted to
promoted to oh and then
very shortly after
they got two stars uh huh
and it's ever
since then they've had the two
Michelin stars
oh my gosh that's
amazing yeah it's really cool
yeah it's very talented
i'm glad she's doing this
it'll be exciting to see yes
Oh well, I think it's coming out now.
Haha
Okay okay 5 ya okay course
I'm covering it haha
Wow but it’s really different
You're coming out
my life is just cooking
it's kitchen
so
I've never been like the woman
or the girl
who's like take care of myself
i was curious to
experience something different
I feel like you trust
when you come to the restaurant
and you trust what I cook
I trust what you say
i wanted to see what i
could look like
Yeah look look yeah look look
2 minutes really perfect
All I thought was that I should send it to you.
There wasn't
This is really the first time
Are you trying Poblame?
Don't be vague or vague.
I'll make it really pretty
As I thought about this
I built three recipes
yes three builds
I think I did a good job with the layers. That’s right.
maybe nude color will be good
brown nude yeah
i like it yeah i like it too
it's nice
when it doesn't steal
the spotlight from the eyes
oh yeah
Stitch some pieces
Stitch by stitch, the original
like hair
I did it with a lot of effort.
Feeling like making clothes
i've always wanted
to have long hair
but it never grows that long so
i've never felt this
it's incredible
it's so beautiful
i could see the dedication
the artist put into it and
when you're an artist
whether you're a chef
makeup hair
it's that little thing that's
pushes you to the top
to be the best
Wow, it's really pretty. It's really pretty.
Wow why did you do so well Wow awesome
5 my god
Wow it's really pretty
Wow
Awesome
Oh, it's awesome
uh 5 my
so beautiful
you guys
i told you right it's beautiful
shh
oh it's beautiful
thank you don't make me cry now
no no way
no way
no no
no tears no tears no tears
amazing thank you guys
it's really nice
i know i have long hair
oh my god it's amazing really
thank you
it's it's so beautiful
don't cry
i love it i'm not crying
and i cried
thank you it's so amazing
you guys did an incredible job
thank you
thank you so
oh my god
they're coming home with me yes
yes take him take him
i'll be i'll be a makeup artist
5 ice cream ice cream ice cream ice cream ice cream
it's very special so thank you
it's so amazing
oh my god
it's my girl
Really
Because I can only have my hair short
What should I do?
Because it changed so dramatically
They say I have hair and that's it
It was a pictorial
I think I'm going to cry too
that's just something with like
feeling
just so beautiful and so secure
and having the hair
that i've never
never had
and then i see myself
in the mirror
over there as well
so i was like who is this girl
so thank you
every time it's hard work
in your beautiful day today
yes definitely
thank you
16 Next Time in Seoul
Yes yes n
16 Next Time Inn
Hull Restaurant
see you again
have a lovely day
Bye bye I was really hungry
I was really hungry
Wow, we've done well now.
Wow, you did really well, right now, right away.
Wow
Well done today, so well until the end
Oh, you worked hard
Oh our Chahong
Teacher, our teacher Chahong
Ah, thank you. Don’t miss it until the end.
finish it quickly
No, but it's really like this
hair makeup
If you change, your life will change
Ah, but
Your expression is so weird, me too
I was sad too
Oh, I became sad. Oh, I was really sad.
Actually, I'm still sad
It's like I just woke up like this.
Oh, what will I do tomorrow?
I'm really looking forward to seeing the number.
Manager, go to work first.
Wow this building is so pretty
The puppy tells me to cheer up
It's good for us
Oh my, oh my, oh my
I feel like I'm going to be crazy today
Just once I thought about it
It's called Ducut.
Covering your hair like this
I'm going to do hair like this
We're just a vintage pantherest
Let's use the material
How do you like it? It’s cool. It’s vintage.
Pantherest, but I like the wave
The wave
It's going to bleed a bit. I'm so passionate.
Actually it is
It's easy to have a wedding with just seven people.
But there is only one of us
Almost like changing one person's life.
Because I change, my performance and
energy and
It takes a lot of time, you know.
uh so we've been together for a long time
It's going to get caught.
Director, a real girl
I think you are the same
Oh, what am I, a girl?
It’s like my mother’s hand, my mother’s hand
girl feeling yes
Oh mom
uh
Haha
no
no ah mom
I'm not saying you're like the director's mother.
He's making fun of me haha
Haha
Really, why do you keep me
It's because it's really cute
It's because the teacher is cute
Like a character
You are so cute baby
Because it’s cute, that’s right, teacher.
Huh, today’s clothes
more and more
The weather doesn't seem to be getting any better
uh
But I can see it a little more today, right?
A little today
It looks warm
Fighting first
Fighting, manager, fighting for our hair salon!
It smells like a beauty salon, but
I think I'm getting used to it
Today will be fun too
There are seven people
Haha I'm not nervous seven
Will I be able to fulfill all my orders?
If these people come now,
So here and now in front of me
This is the couple's clothes
First, 10 cups of rice.
You can assume it doesn't exist.
It's so quick it's time for lunch
You can eat it at one to three o'clock
It would be more comfortable like this, crackle crackle
It doesn't work, it goes back and forth
I guess I'll have to go back and forth.
That's really why I'm the problem
Now that I see the pattern
second third
There is always a delay for customers.
Actually after that
first
second
After sending the guest
I have some free time
So
There's always a logjam between the two.
That's why they don't give me time to eat.
The evil leader is the evil director
Ah, so you took advantage of the opportunity
Let's talk about eating
I'll give it a try
Tell them to do it when it's over, I'll see it again too
See you over the next 10 days
I will talk about it after seeing it.
When I look at it, I will definitely use my phone today.
I have to eat and uh uh
I can't, I can't, I can't hold on, I can't hold on.
I can't see my phone losing weight.
Hold on hold on hold on
I can't see you getting thinner at 40,000.
I heard it, sister
Well, you didn’t eat yesterday.
I must eat lunch
Today I somehow feed you
Oh yeah uh good
somehow
good
yes
For now, hi hi
Hi hi hello nice
To Me 6 Welcome
Welcome to Soy Sauce
welcome
Now, let’s sit down.
Bungeobbang Dalgona, but one more thing
One more bungeoppang
Here is Idol T This Order
Idol T Yes Ah Yes
Yes thank you thank you
there is a
pin in it so you just
if you want you can just like
do this thing sounds good
yeah alright
thank you
Heo Wonbrella has been out all day
Ah, I see.
Are you Korean here? Haha yes.
Haha
Oh, are you Korean? Yes, I’m Korean.
Ah, immigration here
You came when you were thirteen.
Wow, I’m scared of Korean. I’m scared haha. I’m so good at it haha.
I came from Korea last week.
Oh, I went
So, for a moment, Korean
It has increased and it has ah
really one
It's only going to last for a month and then we'll have to burn it again
Ahaha
Are you Korean?
Oh my, I’m so glad to see you.
Oh my, I met you in Korea.
I'm so glad to see you
So
I really wanted to hear Korean
Really
You know English is so difficult.
Oh, you don't know.
Everyone speaks English well.
But hanbok like that
I’m so happy to see people, it’s nice to meet you
Comfortable and ah
This kind of homeland is depicted
Ah
You are here. My guest is here.
No, my friend
The moment my Korean friend is Korean
too suddenly
I was moved to tears
one month
He said he came a month ago and was in Korea.
Oh, then Korea
I guess it still has the smell.
I still have it uh huh huh
Wow, I heard it yet
It hasn’t been that long since you came from Korea.
Haha no sir
This is Sirison
Oh my haha Sirison oh oh oh
I'm American
Oh my gosh
I went on vacation to Korea. Ah, on vacation.
Did I come again?
It's only been a month, so
hello hello
Welcome to our team
Haha hello hello
yes thank you
thank you
yes
hello
Nice to meet you
I will listen to it. Hello, thank you.
thank you
Hello hello uh bag too
Please hello
What do you need
If you have a cell phone or something
Is this your mother’s ninth birthday? Yes yes
Haha Korean
Korean haha
I'm going, so please wear it.
Ha, two
couple of minutes
I think you wore it as a couple look.
Nice to see
Yes, dress comfortably.
Yes, you can follow me.
yes thank you
Nice to meet you yes
Then
what today
special
Do you have an event?
Kay Bury
I heard the story, yes, like this
Yes to the person at home
Special today
Something like new makeup
It's K Beauty, yes
To make it look nice, yes.
I came here ah
Yes hahaha yes it's so good yes
My dad has opened the store now.
As we close
Broadway
All the employees congratulate me like this
I did it
It's popular because of that
you kids
are probably stars oh oh
small deli in the heart
of times square is closing
four of his famous starlight
deli hello
thank you this
seventy one year old routinely
works fourteen hours days
seven days a week
I already came and found the store.
For 39 years since then
I worked
The person from that house
I do Confucianism entirely and I
work entirely
Take charge and do it
After the kids are all grown up,
From next time
My wife started helping me and we worked together at the shop.
In the meantime, I only did 10,000 and Yuga.
almost
I can't care about things like this.
I lived by writing it
So a day like today
my house
Such a great opportunity for people
I wanted to tell you hehehe
yes it's so good
yes then
what style
Do you like makeup?
So that
I just got my double eyelids done not long ago.
So
I didn't know how to do my makeup.
Ah, a little bit now
Because there is swelling
There is also swelling
I'm still excited about this, oh yeah
Because I'm getting older
what makeup
Something too dark or something like that
Not good, yeah
Clean eye makeup like Park Min-young
Haha so much
Just keep the lines clean.
clean skin
How to express
Do you like what you do?
The skin is Park Min-young.
It's so pretty haha
Fixed precision
Your fixation is just um
But it suits me
If you do it, I
Okay ah um yes yes
To my brother, I am just
cut
Well, just a little bit, just a little bit, just a little bit, yeah.
You are taking good care of it
Just manage the swelling a bit more, yes, yes
I think it would be good to use it
When I come out
To my mother
hair first
I think I should do it, mother.
Hair first, yeah
No, my mother too
I said you need to get a cut.
Mom, you need to get a haircut.
That's the state
if mother
If you go in first, my father.
All you have to do is do it.
I have to do it for 2 minutes anyway.
Then those two 10 days
under 2 minutes
I can finish it
Then within those 10 years, Leo
teacher today
I think it will take a while, like yesterday
mother
Oh, you came out
yes hello
Oh hello nice to meet you
Yes, I see you are coming. Nice to meet you.
Yes, the car is coming.
Yes, that's right. Hello, yes.
hello
Nice to meet you, yes ah ah
I need to take care of my hair today
Please, yes.
don't worry yes
You're still pretty
I'll make it prettier, yes yes
Oh, would you like to sit here?
Father, then
In the room over there with me
I'll do it first, yes, yes
It's been a while
It's so nice to meet a Korean person.
Oh yeah yeah
foreigner
It's nice to meet you though
Oh, foreigners keep coming. Yes.
I don't know English
Because it's not perfect
Oh yeah
There were difficulties, so yes
If you want
Do you have a hairstyle? You leave everything to me. You leave everything to me. Yes, I like this hair. Yes, but there are times when I want to change it. Then, maybe you are a little young?
You can let me see it. It's good. It's good.
Oh, it's okay. Oh, are you okay?
Oh, it's an honor to Mr. Cha Hong.
I did my hair and oh my gosh
I'm so glad I did it for you.
Oh, my mother is actually that
15 years of unbalanced cuts
This is the haircut that was popular in Korea before. Do you know Kim Hye-soo's Tacha? It was that haircut back then.
Now the trend of K-beauty itself is
too chic
Don't wear hair that looks too strong.
in Korea
trendy haircut
I hope you give it a try
Now, let me
I've thought about it for a while. Yes.
It's called die cut
Hmm, hair like this is so pretty.
So very much
This is so good, it's true, yeah
It's safe now in Korea
This is trendy hair.
It's pretty so it's a show cut
Clean and short hair
If you tell me exactly, I'll do it for you.
Yes I will do it
I'll give you a dry couple, yes.
You were really welcome today.
Oh, it's so good, of course
You gave me this opportunity
About that, I really
Oh, I think I'm lucky.
This is popular in Korea
Because it's a head, you can drink bottled water.
Well, if you want bottled water, please tell me.
If I cover here
Your face is focused on your eyes.
If these sides are wide
Your eyes and nose become blurred.
But he is like this
If you look at actresses, they cover themselves like this.
Then in your eyes
When I concentrate, my eyes look deep.
The face is more like this
Focusing becomes the center like this
It looks prettier ah
Do you understand? So, what is it?
Looks skinny
I lived without even thinking about this
That diem perm thing I mentioned earlier.
It's hair like this, hmm.
And this head
Do you know what your strengths are? Take a look next to me.
look next to it
The side is really pretty
Look, it's refreshing
Oh, the side is pretty.
And I was worried earlier
Because everything that was covered is covered here.
It's pretty
Oh, it's okay. I like it too. Oh yeah.
And
Look, you sure look young.
Just before
Yes, you can go straight in.
Next bread is here. Yes, yes.
Father, by any chance
Have you ever received something like this? No.
It's my first time. Why? Is it my first time?
Even at weddings
You haven’t tried makeup.
I don't think I did it. Oh, yeah, yeah.
For the first time in my life
Okay, then that's a bit of a greeting.
It's neat
I'll make it visible
thank you
Thanks to my father and mother haha
At the shop
But usually like this
Following me
It's not easy in itself.
That's right
I heard this after this review
Oh really, that's why I'm talking about this
After listening to it, in many ways
I thought it would be good for the people at home.
uh
Oh, that's my father
I recommended it.
Oh really, yeah huh
no why
Uh haha why is it different haha
why
It's different from my husband in Korea.
Haha
Thanks to you, I am now in good spirits.
You are a lover now haha
You are a lover
No, now it's all about work
I got to rest
I'm bored these days
Yes, I'm bored. Yes, right now.
I used to be busy working, but I can't.
What should I do?
If you don't have anything to do, it's a bit difficult, but then do you find time to be yourself?
Oh me, no, mother
I'm curious yes yes
That person has his own
I also had double eyelid surgery hahahaha
Ugh
How did you get it in Korea again?
Uh, as expected
Your makeup will look pretty again.
korean pool
If you have it, it comes out pretty again.
Wow, you'll have fun with this and that
Decorate it
We couldn't do that so uh we
I got married and now have children.
I put three
I'm busy. My wife is trying to take care of the baby.
Yes, I want to make a sandwich.
We divided it up.
I go to work and work at the store.
Yes, my wife decides to only watch the kids now.
Oh, so
I can't even speak well
I can't understand and I can't even go to school
Have it
I have to do many things
How difficult must it have been on this world?
in another country
It was a lot of hard work.
for a while
You've lived a tense life
Now, relax, father.
You still deserve it
Okay I got it
I'll try it
But my father is really perfect
You are a lover
I can see it so much
My personality is yes
A style that takes care of you, yes, yes
Be kind and
Sometimes it's too much, but ahahaha
People really like this uh just other uh people around me
yes
Ta-da, I drew the eyebrows. Yes.
How are you? Thank you.
There are a lot of differences, right?
Yes, how about eyebrows?
Father, please
I summarized it for you. I hope you like it.
It's clean, yes, it's clean
I like it, yeah
Do you like it? I like it. Hehe.
Now, if you sit here
It's over, okay
Thank you, but wash your face
Oh yes, how are you? Father?
Oh, it's clean.
Oh, you can get married again?
I think it's not that bad.
I am learning well. Yes.
yes thank you
Thank you father, now yes
this way
I think you can come and wait a bit.
Kimbap is here. Kimbap is here.
There is no one who can eat it.
eyebrows
than hair
Lighten by one tone or half a tone
Oh, it's so pretty, it looks like a Disney princess
Yes, kimbap is here, but
no one can eat
yes
Teacher Kimbap is here.
Thank you. Please refer to it.
It's in the bathroom over there. Yes, yes.
Oh, that’s right, there is no store.
Hang it at home haha
I heard something from my child's father. How did he come again?
Yeah, I guess I got married in two months.
Did you do it?
It's really been since we met
Yeah, why did you do it so quickly?
What did we do at first?
Well, what are you really in love with?
It wasn't like this, but oh yeah
This is my first time trying it and it’s delicious
Ahaha that
We have a long relationship
It wasn't one marriage, right?
that us
It's been a month since my husband married me
So I went to America.
Uh haha
Not really
You left when we were close
I went there when we weren't friends.
Oh my my
Uhhhh
Just raise the ceremony and then
I left yeah
wedding
You said you left. Yes, just the wedding.
Come to Korea and just get married
So I
Now I waited a year and came in.
I saw you at the airport
It was a little awkward, so strange.
Oh my, what’s strange? It’s been a year since I saw you
Seeing you after a year
I still wanted to see you all this time.
Oh, but when I look at it again, I actually see it
When I actually saw it, aha
It's so strange, my father's ears
You don't have to stop it.
I know everything ah
I know everything
And now
I took the manna and got into the car.
Like this in the car
Put the bouquet like this and oh my
I came, yes, but at that time
In the same heart that broke up with my family
sadness
That's why it was a bouquet and I didn't notice it at the time.
Now it's an apartment
He rented it all himself and
I cooked rice again and said, oh my, honey.
uh
But now that we meet
Oh, people are sincere
Responsible and
I am what I dreamed of
My husband was that kind of person.
Oh my
It was just right, eh
So ah
If this person
It's so good
From then on, I am now completely your husband.
It's this person
There really is only this person.
Oh my oh my
You really make a good impression. Thank you.
Haha
5 my god
Wow hahahahahaha
Are you having fun? Yes.
I think I'm quite satisfied
yes
You’ve completely changed, our dream come to you
Thank you okay bye
Goodbye, good bye
Haha bye
This is my first time seeing this style
This is my first time with this style.
What is that person on TV?
Same
So
People who come out with tough scissors
hair style
Are you going to use Tough Scissors now?
Haha
take a picture
I need to erase it and keep it safe.
I think my daughter will be surprised if she goes.
My daughter is here. Yes.
My daughter is here, right?
Because mom still
I saw the decorations
Dad, this is my first time seeing this style.
This is my first time seeing this in my life
Haha
You're like Papa Guy.
Haha, why am I posting this?
I'm a young person
I see it for the first time, right?
It looks different uh
kinda
Wow kinda
You can see it, just a little hehe.
Doesn't look like a young man
Haha
You feel like you're 20 years younger
Now what
I'm a little scared so I brought it with me.
Uh that
Did you come out? Eat, eat, go and eat.
Oh please eat
The food company is here
Here with kimbap
I think it's a sauce so I'll enjoy it.
Please eat, yes
microphone accessories
It's so cute here
When did you buy that, Mom?
When you leave, tell me to give it to your mom. Ah haha, sweet haha.
Why are there no husbands like that in Korea?
Haha
You're so cool. Yes.
Since you are holding it, yes 5 my god wow
It's pretty, yes, so pretty
As for makeup, what and when?
Have you tried makeup?
This is my first time receiving it.
What is it really? Oh it's real
I have to be good to you.
Oh, will an adult be nice to you?
Something I’ve always been curious about
Yes, ask that.
I can see this right now
You didn't have double eyelids until then.
But at that time I
I put on my makeup with peace of mind.
This is now
Double eyelids appeared
Why can’t I touch you next time?
I can't do it
Oh, how can I do this?
Should I do it?
I don't know what to do
I am
When I saw it, my mother
You have a tattoo on your eye.
This is eyeliner
That
Yeah, it's much better to get rid of this, really.
because of that
It looks more frustrating. Oh my, really.
double eyelid
There's nothing difficult about the line at all
There wasn't one
He got that tattoo.
It got a little thicker
Yes, I have it
You had double eyelid surgery, but
pretty
I can't see any of the lines you captured.
Yes, I just forgot that line
When I saw it, I looked like my mother.
Just like that
You're cute, if I'm being honest.
It makes me feel cute
Oh my, really, but my eyes are a little blurry
There may not be one. That's a laser huh
too
Doesn’t it hurt so much? It hurts. It hurts. Huh.
Oh, I don’t think I can do it. I can’t do it.
Then I
I'll give you a tip. Yes, yes.
What should I do?
Well, what should I do?
A little like this
There is a pencil type concealer.
Like that
Just once on the double eyelid line
Please fill it out
Ah, you can do it naturally.
I'll just see if it's the right color.
Take a look
This is correct.
Look straight ahead
This is becoming more and more obscured.
Can you see my double eyelids?
It's covered up now like this.
Well, compared to the other side
A little like that navy blue
It completely removed and covered up the smudged feeling.
Yeah just like this
Scrub eyeliner
Just do it like I drew it
You can add color. Yes.
Yes, you can do it like this
Look at the scene
Oh, I removed it. Yes, I removed it.
Open your eyes
Wait a minute
Oh my, I was wrong again because I put on eyebrows.
It feels different, I mean.
Huh, I love it, I love it so much
Hey eyebrows
There are so many things that are attached and those that are not attached
There is a big difference, right?
It's so different
The makeup is so pretty
Oh yes now
People are changing like this now
But I can do this alone
How can I do it, but I remember
Now to remember
Do you remember eyebrows, eyebrows, eyebrows?
It's art
Ah, I'm becoming a talent now. Yes.
Yes shoot right away
I think you should go in.
You can let your bangs down, yes.
Now I'm done up there
Oh my your hair is so pretty oh my god you
As soon as I get off, I can feel it.
You're getting younger
This hair suits you really well
Oh so pretty
No, like this
pink color
How are your lips so good?
Do you fit in?
Oh so good now
The feeling just comes to me so well
I think Mr. Heo is really good. Hmm.
Oh mother
They say it really depends on how you decorate, so women
Um, my dad is here.
You changed your face completely, right? You had to put on makeup.
Because
Oh, it's so pretty. What should I do?
Oh, I feel so good
I'm sorry, but it's so fascinating.
Don't go with Chayoung in Korea.
Oh my, what should I do?
Oh my!
I want my hair to be the same though
who does this
Oh my gosh what’s happening huh huh
What should I do, what should I do, you’re perfect
It's a different person, really.
Should we go change clothes now?
Now, mom, are you ready?
It is said that you have become
Yes mom mom ready ahahaha everything
That's it
Yes 5 my god 5 my god haha
your mom's coming yeah
oh my gosh i can't wait
so excited
Ha so different
Yes, I like it haha
Ha, I'm looking forward to it. Yes, I'm so looking forward to it.
Oh my, this
I don't think I'll know what to do
Oh my, what should I do with this?
I don't think you'll recognize me
Oh yeah 5 my god
uh
You're coming out
Haha
5 my god
Something special for my family today
To make it look good
I came here
Then maybe
You can make me look younger.
It's good
Oh well
5 my god
uh
my god
5 tie your hair up
tie your hair
Oh thank you so much
Haha really
Oh, what's going on?
I'm surprised now
That person is me
I feel like she's not my wife
I have become so young and so pretty.
You were pretty when you were young
All in all
I put it on
In the meantime, just do 10,000
Just buy oil
I don't care about the market or anything like that.
I lived by writing it
very hot
The person who made this
People with hairstyles like this
What makes it possible to change
No this
It popped up
I really appreciate it.
5 my god
uh
thank you so much
Really
Oh my, what's wrong with this flower?
It's so delicious, really
Hey, I, I, I was surprised too.
Mom, look at me as a whole.
in the mirror
uh
oh my god look at that
i think
dad's gonna marry her again yeah
so cute
uh
Congratulations thank you so much
No, with my father now
You saved it for 20 years haha.
So pretty, so pretty
It's so pretty, really
I guess I should call him my younger brother now.
Haha
Haha call me sister haha
Just say come from outside haha
Oh my dad’s hair is so funny haha
Oh so funny
Haha
What should I do?
Haha, 2 minutes is really nice to see.
It suits you well. It looks like Nallalari haha.
I was surprised again when I saw myself
I was surprised
Huh, was I this pretty?
It's so pretty
Oh, I feel like I'm 15 years younger haha.
Oh, were you younger?
Oh, I feel so young. Ugh.
You did a really great job.
It was an honor for Nam Ilhan. Yes.
It was nice to meet you
thank you
Goodbye, thank you.
Hahaha
Oh eat something
What do you have, kimbap has arrived
I feel good
I feel better
Wow
Kimbap
um
It's delicious
It's delicious, it's delicious, noona
Sister now
It's been so long since I came here
You were waiting
No, I just waited.
Oh yeah
I'm here now
So now I'm going into counseling, okay?
No problem, okay.
very good
Oh what should I do?
Good job first person
It's the best, yeah
It's the best, it's so pretty, thank you now
It's an illusion
But before I
You have that boyfriend.
But the boyfriend I’ve seen is the most handsome.
You're a bit too handsome
You can't be that handsome
I'm tired. What should other people do?
uh
Look how easy your life is, my brother.
Even if you are very handsome, you should be avoided by others.
Isn't that right? You have to be reasonably handsome.
Yeah
it's like androgynous yeah
like an
like a vampire
what do you think
you like
it it's fantastic
yeah i love it
hey let me try this color
okay
this is
Really famous product in Korea
okay this
finishing is
like this velvet texture
but it's like really
really really light
okay yeah perfect not matte
not too pink but not too orange
it looks really really natural
yeah i know
yeah it's a great color
Yeah it's fantastic
wow okay wow looks so good
here we are
Isn't the hair salon really nice?
We had a festival here.
festival world
I think it's so fun. The atmosphere is so fun.
It suits you well, but today you are swearing
It'll be fun
There's no chaos outside
i'm a taekwondo
athlete
i've been doing taekwondo
Marilyn Monroe for a while
about fifteen years
amazing
oh my gosh
crazy out there right now
okay yeah you guys are great
and i don't really wear makeup
um so it's pretty basic
oh that's my hair
so amazing oh god look at this
I need to impress with makeup.
The older I get, the prettier it gets.
Wow
yeah yeah now life goes up down
or in the middle